What is this?
- I'm a citizen. What about you?
-Me too
What is it? Why is it like that?
Jisoo
No, no, no.
why
Jisoo
i don't want to die
I won't die
I will never let you die
I have to go home
Aren't you going?
Fork
That's me
mafia
It's not you
It's not really!
Hey, don't do that.
Junhee, no, don’t do it!
Hey
Cancel it, quickly say no
Did you find the album?
It's not on the first floor.
no
It was definitely there
Where is it?
Let's find out more
Cha Yu-jun
died
Yujun?
- Cha Yu-jun’s occupation is
- That can't be possible.
I'm a doctor
From now on, all participants
find the mafia
Please start voting
It's not against the rules.
But why...
Did you fall?
I didn't fall
Who killed it?
There are many traces of a struggle.
You have a lot of scars on your head
who attacked
The mafia probably killed him, right?
I don't know
Even if it's the mafia
This isn't real
How can you kill someone when it’s not even night?
What are you going to do now?
I need to find who it is
Why did Yujun come here?
Yoon Seo-ya
Ah, the mafia, you crazy bastards
Are you killing people even during the day now?
Even if Yujun is a doctor
This is too much
Let’s catch the mafia bastard quickly.
fuck
Who are you really?
child, Mr.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
- Oh, why?
- Hey, come to work.
- Hey, why?
What is this?
what?
Junhee and you
The mafia?
Hey, ah, no
I'm not really a mafia
Guys, I, I am a real mafia…
I'm a real citizen, why
Who wrote this, what the hell?
I'm not really
police are capable
Because I wrote it twice
I think two of them are correct.
But earlier, Junhee
You said you were a citizen.
I'm not a mafia either
Don't be rude
Because that was fake earlier
The police must have rewritten it
yes
If you're a real cop, you should write mafia.
Why do you write down citizens?
no
That could be fake
After Yujun died
It's strange that it appeared right away
The person Yujun killed
They want to accuse them of being a mafia
It could be something like that
you guys
Why are you here so late?
Didn’t you guys write this?
If we wrote it, Yoonseo
Don't say that
Ha, fuck, what is this?
hey police
Damn it and come out quickly
Everyone, take out your phone, check your skills.
There's no need for that.
I am the person Yujun killed
I think I know who it is
He said he would tell me who it is.
Why are you here?
in the warehouse
I found shoe prints
I fell next to him
In the shoes of the person Yujun killed
It looks like it fell?
This is the same too
It's strange that we're separated in the middle
I kept remembering
It was because of this
This
It's something that is often attached to basketball shoes.
Basketball shoes?
why? what?
Isn't this yours?
Crazy bitch, what bullshit are you talking about?
Let me see your shoes, check them out
Oh, fuck
I won't add anything like that
You can check it out
Fuck, look, look, huh?
no
Fuck, I said I wouldn’t put it on, Mr.
What? what?
I really don't say that either.
Why the fuck do you keep doubting people?
야, 떳떳하면
그냥 보여 주면 되잖아
- 그래, 봐 봐
- 싫다고
나 아니라고, 씨발
야, 나 아니라고, 씨
하지 말라고, 새끼들아
씨발, 진짜
누구한테 물렸냐?
fuck
Is this really you?
Why did you do that?
not me
I didn't kill you
I also found all the crime tools.
don't lie
fuck
Shall I be honest?
Go Kyung-jun, this bastard killed him.
I really don't!
What is this crazy guy saying?
If you found a shoe and a brick, it's you!
How do you know that?
I didn't say it was a brick
How did you know?
what?
There was one more person in the warehouse besides Jinha.
Same pattern, just no pads
There was one more footprint
Is it you?
Go Gyeongjun
Guys, it's not really me.
This bastard killed it.
What Seungbin killed
This bastard
Fuck it, you got the axe too.
You crazy bastard, fuck…
- Hey, hey, hey!
- 개새끼야, 씨발 새끼
야! don't do it!
- Don't do it!
- Let go, fuck it.
You killed him, you fucking bastard.
Let go, fuck it
Let go, you bastard
Go Gyeongjun!
Let go, let go, fuck
Hey, you crazy bastard!
놔
아, 꺼져, 씨발
야, 이 개새끼야!
Junhee, stop!
Fuck you, come here
Come on, you fucking bastard.
Let go! 와 봐, 이 개새끼야
야! ah! Fuck!
I understand, come out
Hey
What the fuck are you talking about?
Wow, so many different things.
You wrote this, huh?
No, even if it’s like this, this bastard
Not the mafia?
This bastard used it all the time?
What is it?
Did you write the mafia name?
no
I didn't write it!
Hey guys, wait a minute.
Wait, don't do it.
Me, fuck!
I, I really don't know what this is, really
Ah, fuck it, there's an answer.
Vote quickly
not me
Hey, you're the class president!
I don't know what this is
Guys, what's wrong, wait a minute.
Jeongwon, please, wait a minute.
It's so damn
I feel really unfair.
This bastard is a 100% mafia.
Vote and get it over with!
Stop it, Mr.
Yujun killed you too.
Voting will be held at eleven o'clock
You both are in the room.
You guys, don't come out of your room.
Fuck it, it's not even a cell.
What is it?
- Give me the key
-Why?
What if you run away?
Will they kill people again?
How do we know?
Now we're all going to use the canteen together.
Give it to me quickly
No, I lost it.
Don't talk bullshit
Give it to me quickly
Fuck, there isn't any
Then give me your phone
Keep it as collateral
Nowhere without your phone
I won't be able to go
You also killed people
We have to do that much to believe it.
Fuck you, Dabeom
I'll give it to you when you vote
Well, guys
I'm not really a mafia
I didn’t kill Seungbin.
Don't pick on me, okay?
Me, I'm not really
I am a citizen
I have to live so you can live
Hey, here
It's a male, male, men's restroom.
I know
Why?
The safest place here
Where do you think it is?
What does that mean?
speak quickly
Where?
I'm not sure
Ah, this stuff
It's a concession stand.
- Canteen?
- Yeah.
You can’t break the shutter even with an axe.
So?
So what's the point?
Go Kyung-jun's key
let us take it away
I'll add you too
Let's do it together
- Did it hurt?
- No, it's okay.
- Are you okay?
- Yes
thank you
Let’s go once you’ve finished applying the medicine.
You'll be suspicious again that I came late
Yeah
Okay, let's go
let's go
Now I really have to vote
What should I do?
Anyway
Kyungjun seems like a citizen.
Jinha doesn’t know yet
Then
It's right to save Gyeongjun.
But Go Gyeong-jun is also strange.
Why do you kill a doctor when you are a citizen?
That's right
I heard he also had an axe.
Wow, are you stupid?
He also has a key
Why did you break the door?
you really have a head
Did you get a puncture?
I guess they broke it on purpose out of fear of being suspicious.
Fuck, I really don't even know
no
Jinha is weirder
Pretend to be a police officer and write down the kids' names
So
Jinha says Toto
I also borrowed a lot of money from Joo Won.
I don't want to pay the money back
I could have killed him.
Wow, that's it
Yoon Seo-ya
Who do you think is a mafia?
Actually, there's something that's holding me back.
What is it?
If the mafia kills
It says execution.
But why is Yujun
Did it say death?
It could be because they die during the day.
if
What if Jinha and Gyeongjun are both citizens?
So what?
Why is it so complicated
Do you think?
You two killed Yujun together.
just
Tell them both not to vote
No way
If you kill them all like that
What's different from them?
yes
Don't talk nonsense
Then the police should at least use their powers!
Of the two, the one who is a citizen
You can save it
Yeah, that's for sure
No way
The doctor died too
The police will be more burdened now.
Don't force it
You're leaving a message right now.
It's more complicated now because of that.
Ah, that's it, that's it, that's it
First of all, to whom
Let's decide whether to vote first.
So everyone has decided?
Okay?
But
What should I do with this?
I have to bring it to you
You also need to tell me the voting results.
Then
Who's going to get it?
Let's all go together?
I'll do it
You vote first and then hide
If everyone hides
I'll get you the phone then.
I do the same
You can give this to each person.
take it
고경준, 이 개새끼
너는?
Did you do it?
Fuck, really
please
Uh, Jun, Junhee.
Hey Junhee
I really
I'm not really, huh?
I'm a real citizen
Please, save me just once
I really don't want to die
Huh? Junhee, please
Jinhaya
Yujun must have wanted to live too.
So get insurance
I should have listened
What?
아니야
빨리 폰 갖고 오라 그래
니 폰 없어
열쇠 어디 있는지 말해 줘
그럼 줄게
개새끼가 돌았나, 씨
너 혼자
절대 못 찾아
투표 못 하면 어떻게 되는지 알지?
Where are the keys?
Our Dabeom has grown up a lot, huh?
I know how to threaten
Follow me, there's no time.
go
What is it? Oh, there isn't one.
Okay?
Now give me your phone
If you need a key
I shouldn't have said
It scares people for no reason, huh?
Where are you?
Hey there
you brought it
Is that real or not?
How do I know?
맘대로 해, 난 갈 거야
가지고 오라고, 이 씨발 새끼야
시간도 없는데 괜찮겠어?
It's funny, you fucking idiot!
Hey, open it
Open it, you dog...
Ah, you fucking bastard!
열어, 열어, 이 개새끼야
열라고, 이 개새끼야
야, 열어!
Open! 열어, 이 씨발 새끼야
진다범 이 씨발 새끼야!
If you leave I will kill you
You fucking bastard
open it, fuck
Hey! Jindabeom!
hey! Fuck!
Oh, fuck!
voting
It has ended
Jinha Kim, the person with the most votes
will be executed
fuck
No way
Jinha Kim’s occupation is
I am a citizen
Hey, what is it?
Jinha Kim was a citizen?
Were you a citizen?
Ha, fuck, fucked.
The mafia bastards will be caught and killed tomorrow.
i will kill you
You fucking bastard
How do you feel about being bullied by a bully?
Very shit, right?
Kyungjun
The mafia
Set a target unanimously
They're all coming
You fucking bastard!
fuck
fuck you bastard
Fuck you bastard
Die, you fuck.
Ouch! Fuck!
It's about time, you asshole.
Fuck, you're hitting me so hard it hurts
fuck you bastard
What the fuck
What the fuck, don’t come!
fuck
Wow, I was so surprised.
Kyungjun
when a person dies
This hearing until the very end
They say he's alive
Think of me while listening to this